marutisuzukistingray.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Maruti Suzuki India Limited

**Maruti Statement of Privacy** At Maruti we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our terms and conditions.

###  What the terms and conditions cover

This covers Maruti's treatment of personally identifiable information that Maruti collects when you are on Maruti Suzuki site and when you use our services. This policy also covers Maruti's treatment of any Personally identifiable information that Maruti shares with you.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Maruti does not own or control or Maruti does not own or employ or manage.

###  Information Collection and Use

Maruti collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Maruti account. When you choose the services and promotions. Maruti may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

When you register with Maruti, we ask for your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, occupation, industry and personal interest. Once you register with Maruti and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Maruti uses information for three general purpose: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services and to contact you about specials and new products.

###  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Maruti will not sell or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to anyone.

Maruti will send Personally Identifiable Information about you when:

We have consent to share the information

We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested

We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

When we find your action on the web site violates the Maruti terms and condition or any of your usage guidelines for specific products or services.

###  Security

Your Maruti account information is password-protected for your privacy and security We have taken adequate measures to secure access to your personal data?

###  Changes to this Policy

Maruti may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes ,we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
